<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab04</string>
    <string name="stupid">Text: Stewart, James, Multivariable Calculus, 4th Ed. Brooks/Cole Publishing, Pacific Grove, California 1999, ISBN 0-534-35948-5, and Replacement Cost: $100 Course Description: This course is equivalent to a third semester college calculus course. Differential and integral calculus of several variables are the focal points of this college-level course which extends the advanced placement calculus experience to three dimensions, culminating in the calculus applications to physics with Stokes\', Green\'s and Gauss\' Theorems. An additional 0.50 quality point will be added to the quality point value assigned to the final grade earned in this course. Each institution in accordance with local policies grants appropriate credit and placement. Homework/Homework Quizzes: On the first day of school, a schedule of assignments and answers to even-numbered questions is distributed for the semester. The schedule is also available through Blackboard. Homework will not be collected or graded for credit. There will be time in each class to ask questions about the homework. There will be approximately eight Homework Quizzes worth 20 points each. Students may use their homework, for the corresponding assignments, to complete the quiz. It is important that students work to understand the material. Each student is allowed to miss (and not make up) one quiz per quarter (assuming an excused absence/tardy) without penalty. Tests: Tests are administered at the end of each chapter and will be worth approximately 100 points. They will include material from previous chapters in order to maintain a constant review process. Retakes: Students scoring below 80% on the Ch13-4, Ch15 or Ch16 test, will be permitted one retake on ‘retake day’. Cumulative Grade: This class will use a semester-long, running gradebook. Given the disparity of the time in each quarter, this will give a more accurate representation of each student’s overall grade in the course. No one assignment will greatly impact the overall grade in the course and the current overall grade will always be known using the online gradebook. The end-of-semester grade will be based on a semester-long gradebook, which will be worth 80% of the overall grade for the course. The final exam will be worth 20% of the overall grade for the course. Grading: The FCPS grading scale is: B+ (87-89) 3.3 C+ (77-79) 2.3 D+ (67-69) 1.3 A (93-100) 4.0 B (83-86) 3.0 C (73-76) 2.0 D (64-66) 1.0 A- (90-92) 3.7 B- (80-82) 2.7 C- (70-72) 1.7 F (below 64) 0.0 Make-up work and Extra help: Plan ahead. If you know you will be absent, get assignments early and make arrangements to take any missed assessments. It is your responsibility to get any make-up work or extra help, if needed. All tests must be made up within one week during 8th period make-up. Register in advance for Math/CS Make-up during 8th period. If you cannot make up the work within a week then you must make other arrangements with your teacher ahead of time or you will receive a zero. Extra help is also available during 8th period by signing up for MV tutoring. A student who knows they will not be in class for a test is strongly encouraged to take it earlier. A later make-up within a week of the original test day will be possible but it will take away the retake opportunity on that test. Blackboard: We will use Blackboard to provide you with pertinent class-related information, including this policy statement and the current assignment sheet. Please make sure your BB email address is the one you check most frequently. Registration for College Credit: Information for getting College credit for this course from George Mason University will be posted on Blackboard once it becomes available to us. This is optional. For those of you who are interested in this dual enrollment opportunity, we strongly recommend that you work with GMU to follow the guidelines that should be posted on blackboard by mid-September. Cellphone Policy: Per FCPS policy, electronic devices are only allowed during passing, lunch, and 8th period. Cell phones may not be used during instructional time without explicit permission from your teacher. This includes bathroom breaks during class. Students in violation of this policy will have their cellphone confiscated and will be referred to administration. FCPS, TJHSST, and Classroom Policies:  Students are expected to adhere to the dress guidelines put forth by Fairfax County Public Schools.  Students are expected to attend every class on time. The FCPS attendance policy and procedures are followed in this course.  Students are expected to adhere to the network user guidelines (also called appropriate use policy). All violations are reported. Loss of computer and network</string>
</resources>
